It is everything you've dreamed of. It is nothing you expect.
Cocoon is a comedy, science fiction, mystery film directed by Ron Howard.
When a group of trespassing seniors swim in a pool containing alien
cocoons, they find themselves energized with youthful vigor.
Jack Bonner, played by Steve Guttenberg.
Kitty, played by Tahnee Welch.
Walter, played by Brian Dennehy.
Arthur Selwyn, played by Don Ameche.
Benjamin Luckett, played by Wilford Brimley.
Joseph Finley, played by Hume Cronyn.
Cocoon is a 1985 American science fiction comedy drama film directed by Ron
Howard and written by Tom Benedek from a story by David Saperstein.
The film stars Don Ameche, Wilford Brimley, Hume Cronyn, Brian Dennehy, Jack Gilford, Steve Guttenberg, Maureen Stapleton, Jessica Tandy,
Gwen Verdon, Herta Ware, Tahnee Welch, and Linda Harrison, and follows a group of elderly people rejuvenated by aliens.
The film was shot in and around St.
Petersburg, Florida, with locations including the St.
Petersburg Shuffleboard Club, Suncoast Manor Retirement
Community, the Coliseum, and Snell Arcade buildings.
The film earned Academy Awards for Best Supporting Actor (Don Ameche) and Best Visual Effects, and was followed
by the sequel Cocoon: The Return in 1988, in which almost all of the original cast returned.
The film explores themes of florida, swimming
pool, alien, mahjong, boat trouble.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.